<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JStock U.S. Investing</title>
    <link>https://investing.jstock.co/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JStock U.S. Investing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://investing.jstock.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>https://investing.jstock.co/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://investing.jstock.co/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Who are we? Yocto Enterprise, business registration no. 002598402-W develops and distributes JStock Android and JStock Desktop, to provide users with the ability to purchase selected securities listed on United States stock exchanges, including fractional interests in those securities.
When you sign up using JStock Android or JStock Desktop, you agree to commence the application process for a:
 DriveWealth, LLC US brokerage account.  We have entered into a Foreign Finder Agreement with DriveWealth, LLC (DriveWealth).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accounts</title>
      <link>https://investing.jstock.co/accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 15:40:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://investing.jstock.co/accounts/</guid>
      <description>Can I try for free? Yes, you can open a FREE Practice Investing Account by simply providing your First Name, Last Name and Email. You will be given $10,000 virtual cash which you can use to get comfortable with investing for as long as you like.
Practice Accounts
They are open 24&amp;frasl;7 but prices only update during normal market hours.
They are available to users risk free, at no cost &amp;amp; for educational purposes only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deposit &amp; Withdrawal</title>
      <link>https://investing.jstock.co/deposit-withdrawal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 15:40:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://investing.jstock.co/deposit-withdrawal/</guid>
      <description>How to deposit money? While your account application is under review, you may already start deposit money into your account. Just click on PENDING APPROVAL, choose your desired deposit method to deposit.
If your account is already approved, just click on CASH DEPOSIT.
Payment methods for deposit To deposit funds into your Live Investing Account, the following methods are available:
 Linked Bank Account (ACH) - U.S. client Only Charge Cards - We accept Visa, Mastercard, Discover and American Express Wire Transfer USD Check Western Union Dwolla - U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing</title>
      <link>https://investing.jstock.co/investing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 15:40:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://investing.jstock.co/investing/</guid>
      <description>Where is dividends paid? If you own a company that pays dividend in your Live Investing Account, these funds will be paid into your account. Once deposited, you can decide what to do with these funds - reinvest back into new investments, keep them in cash in your account or withdraw the money.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>